[
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜‚",
        "response": "ğŸ˜‚"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜",
        "response": "ğŸ˜"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤£",
        "response": "ğŸ¤£"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜œ",
        "response": "ğŸ˜œ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¥³",
        "response": "ğŸ¥³"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤—",
        "response": "ğŸ¤—"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜",
        "response": "ğŸ˜"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜±",
        "response": "ğŸ˜±"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜",
        "response": "ğŸ˜"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜‡",
        "response": "ğŸ˜‡"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¥º",
        "response": "ğŸ¥º"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤”",
        "response": "ğŸ¤”"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ™ƒ",
        "response": "ğŸ™ƒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜¬",
        "response": "ğŸ˜¬"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜’",
        "response": "ğŸ˜’"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¥µ",
        "response": "ğŸ¥µ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜…",
        "response": "ğŸ˜…"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜´",
        "response": "ğŸ˜´"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜·",
        "response": "ğŸ˜·"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤­",
        "response": "ğŸ¤­"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜º",
        "response": "ğŸ˜º"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ™ˆ",
        "response": "ğŸ™ˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¥¸",
        "response": "ğŸ¥¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤“",
        "response": "ğŸ¤“"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜¤",
        "response": "ğŸ˜¤"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜³",
        "response": "ğŸ˜³"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜©",
        "response": "ğŸ˜©"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜µ",
        "response": "ğŸ˜µ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜µâ€ğŸ’«",
        "response": "ğŸ˜µâ€ğŸ’«"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜¤",
        "response": "ğŸ˜¤"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜”",
        "response": "ğŸ˜”"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜¡",
        "response": "ğŸ˜¡"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜ˆ",
        "response": "ğŸ˜ˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤¡",
        "response": "ğŸ¤¡"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¥º",
        "response": "ğŸ¥º"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ‘€",
        "response": "ğŸ‘€"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ˜‹",
        "response": "ğŸ˜‹"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ‘½",
        "response": "ğŸ‘½"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ’©",
        "response": "ğŸ’©"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ‘Œ",
        "response": "ğŸ‘Œ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "ğŸ‘‘"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ’”",
        "response": "ğŸ’”"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ¤Ÿ",
        "response": "ğŸ¤Ÿ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸ‰",
        "response": "ğŸ‰"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒˆ",
        "response": "ğŸŒˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒ»",
        "response": "ğŸŒ»"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸƒ",
        "response": "ğŸƒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒŠ",
        "response": "ğŸŒŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒ¼",
        "response": "ğŸŒ¼"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒ",
        "response": "ğŸŒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ø¬ÙŠØ¨ Ø§Ù„Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ø¯Ù‡ ğŸŒ™",
        "response": "ğŸŒ™"
    }
]
